myapne.com 2014-03-10

# Apne TV Hindi Serials Online | Punjabi Movies | Songs | Radio | News | Bollywood Videos

## Privacy Policy

We are committed to ensure that privacy of a user is never compromised at Apne.tv. We take your right to privacy seriously, and wants you to feel comfortable using this web site. This privacy policy enlightens you with the personally-identifiable information (referred to as "data" below) that may be collected by this site, please read carefully and also free to contact us at _ **contact@myapne.com**_ for any additional questions.. This policy does not apply to other entities that are not owned or controlled by the site's owner, nor does it apply to persons that are not employees or agents of this website.

**Data Collection**

One does not need to register in-order to use this website's products or services. We never ask for an email address or name or any kind of information from the user. We respect the right of privacy for a user as a result we do not collect any information from any user visiting this site. Thus Data collection of any sort does not exist on this site.

**Use of Data Collected**

This Site does not collect any kind of data at all. We highly discourage collecting data as we respect the right of privacy and thus no data is stored in our system and user visiting this site is completely secured and thus his privacy would not be compromised thorugh this website

**Web Cookies**

Like many web sites, this web site sets and uses cookies to enhance your user experience -- to remember your personal settings, for instance. Advertisements may display on this web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer; such cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the parties providing the advertisement. However, the parties providing the advertising do not have access to this site's cookies. These parties usually use non-personally-identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to this site.

**Sponsers**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org.

**Regulated**

The Privacy policy of this website would be regulated on constant basis in-order to ahere to the current standards of privacy in the online world. It is our responsibilty to ensure that user feels comfortable using this website and we would keep ensuring that our policies are upto mark.

**Contact Info**

Please contact us at contact@apne.tv for any questions and we do not take any responsibilty for any factors that are not in-control of the site's owner that would result in breach of privacy.
